Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
MARINE CORPS FINAL EXERCISE - BELIZE
In a tent in Belize.
one man prepares for the ultimate test.
His look. determined.
His ass. wet
from the warm shit.
trickling down his leg.
Shut your mouth.
- Dude.
- Hurry.
Tonight you'll be a marine.
Numbskull. one minute left.
Yeah. yeah.
Every fucking time. huh?
Relax.
- I'm all hyped.
- Dude. I'm always hyped.
That's true.
All right. dickhead.
- Are you ready?
- Let's do this.
Crew. rally.
Faster. faster.
1.200 MILES AWAY - CARIBBEAN SEA
ZR.MS. GRONINGEN PATROL VESSEL
Attention. bridge here.
FRISC has been launched. out.
FRISC released.
Mother. FRISC here.
FMS operators on board. on our way.
Roger. Go-fast north of you. one mile.
Welcome.
Hey. fat ass.
First female fucking marine. eh?
First female marine. dude.
- They're gone.
- Okay. get your ass moving.
- Dump it.
- Faster.
They're dumping.
Mother. Roger. mark 12.327130.
three contraband.
We're closing in. stand by for boarding.
Go!
Mother. FRISC here.
They're turning starboard. course 045.
You're gonna make history.
Keep smiling. right?
See you down there.
- This is Papa 843. Approved?
- Papa 843. this is Coast Guard.
Visual on Go-fast.
Request permission for disabling.
Papa 843. approved.
Execute.
We got him. Bull's-eye. Bull's-eye.
Yep. it's done. Nice one.
The Go-fast is slowing down.
I repeat.
The Go-fast is slowing down. Out.
On a roll. man.
Come on. man.
What the fuck?
Execute boarding.
Weapons ready.
- Everybody down! Everybody down! Hands up!
- Here! Here!
Don't move!
Kneel!
Hands on your head! Go!
We got them.
Go-fast secured.
Three tangos and kilos of coke.
It's a big catch.
- Good job.
- Nice.
You're not a pussy. come on.
A marine who's afraid of heights
is a no. Lanshof.
It happens. End of story.
MAMBO BEACH - CURACAO
Dad. Dad.
Dad. look.
Exercise?
No. it's not one of ours.
It's the flag of Veragua.
What is happening?
People. get out of the water. Out!
Ladies and gentlemen--
Kenny!
Captain?
FRISC. Mother here.
Abandon mission. return at once.
I repeat. abandon mission.
What the...
You thought. "I know a better route?"
Shit. I'm out.
Men. listen up!
Pack up and leave. now.
Judsel.
Curacao is under attack.
Attack?
We have to get back to Aruba now.
Shit has hit the fan.
By whom?
Veragua. No idea why.
That's all we know.
Get to the chopper now.
Airborne in five minutes.
Come on. move it. Go. go. go!
INVASION
MARINE CORPS
MARINE BARRACKS SAVANETA - ARUBA
This is Daniel Martina. the guard.
Close the fucking gate.
They're here as well.
We're under attack.
Close that fucking gate. man!
- Shit.
- Major.
What the fuck are those guys doing here?
No idea.
Okay. okay.
This is the gate. we're here.
Ammunition. armory.
One problem. everyone's on leave.
and the armory is locked.
And the key to the ammo bunker is here.
Oh. shit!
I know where it is. I'll go get that key.
Cover me. okay?
Shit!
My god. Here goes nothing! Fuckers!
AMMUNITION BUNKER
CARIBBEAN SEA
Sergeant. we're not going to Savaneta?
We can't go back. Aruba is under fire.
We divert to the Groningen.
Approaching Mother. stand by.
As soon as we land everyone gets out.
Moments ago.
Veraguan forces invaded our country.
HOSPITAL - CURACAO
They have taken control of Curacao
through the use of military force.
All inhabitants of Curacao...
Hey. Jesus. Carl.
What did you do now. crazy old man?
Andy and Judsel. we have to--
I just called Judsel. okay?
He's still on the ship.
I told him about your situation.
I'm not going anywhere. I'm staying here.
Coastguard for Mother. we are inbound.
Dropping off marines.
Go. go. We have to go back.
Andy!
Dad's in the hospital.
- He's one of the victims.
- What?
The resort was attacked.
Jesus.
Isa is with him. she's keeping me updated.
- I have to go there.
- You can't.
I sure can. I'm out.
- Out?
- Where's your captain?
I also want to go there. but--
Never mind. I'll find him myself.
Show of force. gather intel.
don't intervene. Got it.
Captain.
I'm sorry. but I have to leave this ship.
Excuse me. This is my older brother.
He's had a bad day. so he doesn't mean--
I do mean it.
Our father is in the hospital.
- Everyone stays on board.
- Captain. we're useless on board.
Yes. but these are government orders.
It's a crisis. so no trainees.
But we finished our training today.
I'm out.
Can I go?
- You're out?
- Yes.
You think this is a TV show? Survivor?
I don't care what it is.
You're dressed like a soldier.
so behave like one.
And if I don't?
Attention. Captain and Chief Officer.
come to the bridge.
You think this is Survivor?
What a dickhead.
We're not allowed to do anything at all.
Just sit still and shut up. great.
Are you okay?
Sure. it's my dad.
He once fell down the cargo hold
of a freighter. 20 feet down.
Not a scratch.
It'll be all right.
Hey. Our barracks in Savaneta
are under attack.
- What?
- I just heard your brother say that.
- Fuck. now what?
- How should I know?
Nothing. I guess.
Gather intel. that kind of bullshit.
You'd think. I don't know. they could
use a few extra fucking marines.
What are they doing? They need us there.
You guys maybe.
I couldn't even get off that tiny rock.
Left.
What do these guys want?
How do I know? Don't whine. just run.
Go. go. go!
Grab what you can carry.
Guns.
Let's hope the keys are in there.
Faster. bro!
It can't go faster!
No. faster!
Shit. those guys. Up there!
Bro!
There. on the left!
Go left!
Fuck!
To your left. sit back.
- Stay calm. marine!
- I am fucking calm!
This morning. the coast of Curacao
came under fire from Veraguan warships.
This left several dead and dozens wounded.
The attack comes as a surprise.
Veragua has claimed
the ABC islands for decades.
But it had never come to an attack.
The relations between Veragua
and the islands have worsened of late.
In January. President Cruz declared
the islands to be "outlawed."
You are not alone.
With the main military targets
under Veraguan control.
we can speak of an occupation.
Look. behind me. This was my house.
The attack has led to an outcry.
and today the Defense Ministry
will brief the press.
Aruba. Bonaire. and Curacao are part
of the Kingdom of the Netherlands.
DEFENSE OPERATION CENTER - THE HAGUE
DEFENSE CRISIS CONTROL CENTER
Thank you.
At war?
What the hell are we going to do?
I assume you've already
called Curacao and Aruba?
Yes.
Officially contact the Americans?
- Can't they invoke Article 5?
- It doesn't apply.
It's about the only piece of land
they haven't laid a claim to.
The one who's stolen it has to solve it.
So we're on our own.
Who do we have in Veragua?
Maurits Caan.
Oh. God. I thought he was in Luxembourg.
I'll call him.
NETHERLANDS EMBASSY - VERAGUA
- Caan.
- Maurits. we have a problem.
What on earth is going on over there?
They're putting barbed wire
outside my door. Janice.
- Do you know why Cruz has attacked?
- You don't get it.
Cruz is about to be toppled.
so he needs a stunt.
- So?
- So this is it.
This is his stunt.
But still. he needs a reason. an excuse.
Right?
You don't invade for no reason.
What do your contacts say?
Nothing. No idea where they are.
Don't we have you there to know that?
- My staff is gone.
- What do you mean "gone"?
Gone. bye. vanished.
Only my assistant is still here.
And considering the situation.
I don't blame them.
We've tried every diplomatic avenue here.
Or do you want me to stay here
for a few lost backpackers?
Listen. Maurits. You stay there.
whatever happens. Is that clear?
You'll be safe at the embassy.
Maurits. I mean it.
Sure. of course. I'd be delighted to.
BREAKING NEWS
ARMORY
Friendly. friendly.
Go. go!
Two minutes. free shopping.
Vests. guns.
Your sister-in-law is with him. right?
Call her. Ask her how he's doing.
I don't know her.
I've never met her.
I think she does scenic flights
over Curacao.
That's all I know.
Does that matter?
You know. nothing personal against you.
but this sulking isn't gonna help anyone.
We're here to defend things.
So jump into the water. swim with
the dolphins to your dad. nick a FRISC...
or stay here and help us.
But choose which side you're on.
Okay?
Is this everyone?
No. Major.
There are a few guys at the cell block.
guarding a prisoner.
They're under crazy fire.
Prisoner?
Yeah. apparently. he's very important
to the Veraguans.
Okay. reload and head there.
You still have that annoying thing?
Enemy approaching from the north.
- Keep your eyes open.
- Ready?
Covering fire!
Next. move up!
Team two. move up!
There's a fucking lot of them!
Come to the left.
Behind that car!
Last man!
Kill him!
Goddammit!
Kill them!
Okay.
Now or never.
Keep covering.
Reload.
Guard the door.
Is that him?
As it turns out.
we have a diplomat in jail in Aruba.
The former Veraguan Chief of Intelligence.
Jesus Christ.
This is a big misunderstanding.
He just said he's some diplomat.
And who is this diplomat?
Lagarto. Hector Lagarto.
He arrived in Aruba
as the new consul general.
but he is wanted by the U.S.
for drug trafficking.
So he was arrested at the airport.
Due to his resistance. the local police
handed him over to the Dutch Marines.
But they shouldn't have arrested him.
Diplomatic immunity. which explains
why that Cruz guy is so pissed off.
If you don't believe me. fine.
You leave me here or you let me go.
No difference.
I am of no importance.
And this Lagarto is now...
With us. at the Savaneta barracks
in Aruba. which is under heavy fire.
Lagarto's detention is used by Cruz
as an excuse to attack the islands.
Then I propose that we let him go.
Pardon?
We declare him persona non grata
and end this crap.
Mr. Prime Minister. this is an invasion.
He'll come with us.
We must get Lagarto out
before the base falls.
- Send frigates.
- Absolutely not.
- No more escalation.
- It's already escalated.
There is a diplomatic solution.
and we will find it.
New plan!
Get him out of his cell.
You. change your clothes.
Hold your fire!
Cover. here.
Did they see us?
Negative.
Guard the door.
Friendly!
Everyone still in one piece?
- Check.
Check.
Can't we just cut him loose and look away?
- No way.
- Major.
With all due respect. is this worth it?
Locking him up was a wrong decision.
So?
So take positions.
Put a 360 on all windows and doors.
NETHERLANDS EMBASSY - VERAGUA
Come on in.
Sir. the building is empty
and still clean after the last round.
Is there anything else I can do for you?
Okay. move it. Marjon. Go!
This is a pretty stupid idea.
- We're safe at the embassy.
- No. we're out of here.
- Step on it.
- Okay.
The airport is to the left.
- Fuck. it's blocked. To the right! Jesus!
- Come on.
Calm down.
Jesus.
DEFENSE OPERATION CENTER - THE HAGUE
Janice.
The embassy in Veragua is empty.
What do you mean "empty"?
We've received word that Caan has run off.
What?
Apparently. he's fled.
Maurits Caan has run off.
ZR.MS. GRONINGEN - CARIBBEAN SEA
Okay. got it.
Government orders.
Our ambassador is on the run in Veragua.
If they catch him. they can blackmail us
by using him as a bargaining chip.
And we have to get him out?
We're not manned for that.
But our marines stuck in Savaneta
won't last much longer.
They're with a corrupt diplomat
who has to get out of there now.
So we'll pick them up and get them to--
Veragua?
Those guys will be exhausted.
Judsel. it was that
or I'd never get them out of there.
The Hague doesn't want to do anything.
I need an excuse
to get the chopper flying.
They're under heavy fire.
Prepare the Cobra. extraction is a go.
I have to call an old friend.
Now what?
The first plane out of here.
I don't care where it's going.
I'm so done with this fucking country.
SANTA MARTA INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
CLOSED RED GATE
Shit.
You see? Now we're fucked.
Just show them your passport.
Just show them.
Mine is diplomatic. they'll see who I am.
I don't think they're looking for you.
Well. I do.
Jesus Christ. woman.
Move over. I'm driving.
Let's get out of here.
I know a better place. a safe one.
Hold on.
NO MORE REPRESSION
Hurry. hurry. hurry. Get them!
Hello?
Hey. Crocodile Dundee.
Are you still alive?
Yeah. but Crocodile Dundee
could use some assistance.
How bad is it?
It's beautiful here.
I see the sun.
It's even better here.
You're full of shit.
I swear. Come see for yourself.
There's a chopper on its way.
Be ready in four minutes.
ZR.MS. GRONINGEN - COMMAND CENTER
Chopper is airborne. Maximum support.
- Where's the chopper?
- Check.
- Aerial view?
All right guys. get up.
Pickup at the helipad.
Let's go.
Outside is clear.
Move.
- Helo one minute out.
- Check.
Go.
Helo to Mother. Approaching LZ.
approaching LZ. 30 seconds out.
We got a visual.
Well done. Stan. Well done.
Yes. there they are!
Target in sight. seven max.
I repeat. seven max.
There. there. there!
Taking too much fire here.
Docking off. Docking off.
Keep firing. keep firing!
Hey! What the fuck is this? Fuckers!
LZ under heavy fire.
Unable to extract.
Cover. cover. cover!
Major!
Put pressure on the wound!
We're fucked!
You think?
Secure the asset.
We can't hold on any longer!
What are we going to do?
- Go to the FRISC.
- No.
I'll cover you.
Shit!
Go. marine.
Fuck! Come on. come on! Come on. come on!
Up! Up!
Come on. to the FRISC!
Go. marines. go!
Go!
Come on. come on! Go!
- Jump! Jump!
- Jump! Jump! Jump!
Keep going! Go!
Start the engine!
Sorry. captain. but...
what do we do with that ambassador?
What. Caan?
Yeah. without those marines
to pick him up...
Permission for a crazy suggestion.
My brother's platoon.
aren't they deployable?
CARDON GOLF CLUB
The ambassador is on the run.
and The Hague says he's in danger.
I know this isn't standard procedure.
but we have no choice.
So you're our last hope.
We'll do an emergency evac
behind enemy lines.
I need two of you for this.
Marine Prins. Marine Lens. execute.
We take position off the Veraguan coast.
You pick up the asset. return.
and we leave their territorial waters.
Understood?
Yes!
We're gonna pick up a sweaty diplomat.
- Easy. right?
- All in a day's work.
Back in a bit.
You better be.
NORTHERN COAST - VERAGUA
Ladies and gentlemen.
entering Veraguan airspace. be aware.
Four minutes out.
Not a word. Lanshof.
Yes.
Helmet cams live.
Thank God. Okay. thank you. Thank you.
It's chaos.
What?
The rebels have taken over.
and troops are headed this way.
But a chopper is coming to pick us up.
so if we just stay calm--
Calm? If it's late.
they can scrape us off the lawn.
- They say they're close.
- The Dutch army says a lot.
Prepare for the worst.
In this country. no one keeps a promise.
Area looks secure. We're going in.
Asset in sight.
Evac. in and out!
Come on!
Enemy from the east.
Incoming.
Go. go. go!
Asset secured.
This is coastguard to Mother.
Package is cleared.
Extraction accomplished.
Try to stay low to avoid radar detection.
On our way back. See you in a bit.
- Lagarto now on board.
- Check.
Incoming. ten o'clock!
I see smoke.
Fuck. engine failure.
We're losing hydraulic pressure.
Try rebooting all systems.
Rotor overheating.
Stand by for cross-check now.
System malfunction.
Coast Guard for Mother. we've been hit.
Going in decline. Losing altitude fast.
Tail is about to go out.
Tail rotor failure.
Secure both engines.
Declining fast.
Mayday. mayday. mayday.
Multiple hits.
Emergency landing.
We're going down. We're going down.
Mayday! Mayday!
Mother to Coast Guard. Radio check.
- Radio check. Radio check.
- Nothing at all?
Connection down.
transponder still working.
We've lost them.
What do you mean "lost"?
Do something. Send a second chopper.
There is no second chopper.
I'm sorry.
Fuck!
We don't know if they're dead.
Maybe they're still alive.
He can't do anything.
Stan. there's nothing he can do.
The Hague doesn't want it.
Maybe we do.
Isa. your wife.
She does scenic flights
over Curacao. right?
Yeah.
Can't she fly me to Veragua
under the radar?
Yes.
But that means you'll have to jump.
I know.
Secret mission. guys?
Well. brief me then.
He's coming to Curacao. and then?
I can't leave.
We're out of options. Isa.
This is insane. You know that. right?
I thought you liked a bit of insanity.
Okay. so I'll fly over a dictatorship
and throw your brother out of a plane?
I don't even know him.
Sorry. honey. I can't fly.
You can do this. You'll be fine.
Okay. let's do it.
Baby. you're a champ.
We're going covert.
Attention. black hole in force.
We're going covert. Out.
Our best operators.
They'll get you to Curacao unseen.
Tracking device. to find the chopper.
- Coordinates?
- In there.
GPS phone.
Give me a sitrep
when you get to the crash site.
Find them. and if they're still alive.
get them to the beach.
- Ready?
- Yes.
Let's go.
We'll wait for you
at the ready point offshore.
If we're detected. you're on your own.
Off you go.
See you on the other side.
FRISC released.
Noa?
Noa!
Nah. I'm totally fine.
Where's Noa?
- Noa. where is she?
- Who. what?
1 MILE AWAY FROM CURACAO
Clear. Good luck.
Noa!
Hey!
Are you okay? Can you stand?
Wow. fuck!
- That's bad.
- Take it out.
No. I think you shouldn't take it out.
Take it out.
Fuck!
Bite.
Okay.
Yes? Ready?
Come.
Jesus. you look like your bro--
Isa. Nice to meet you. Andy. I presume?
How's Dad?
Fine. he's alive.
Come on. we have to hurry.
Attention! Attention!
- Go. go. go!
- It is forbidden to go outside.
Violations will be punished.
Attention! Attention!
It is forbidden to go outside.
Lend me a hand?
- Are you okay?
- Fear of heights.
- Turns out I have it.
- Which kind?
There are two kinds.
With the first one.
you're also scared on a roller coaster.
That's a fear of falling.
With the second one.
you're afraid to jump.
So then you can fuck it up yourself.
- Well?
- The second.
You can fuck things up in your own time.
Come.
Should we bury them?
I don't think so. pal.
Those guys who shot us down
know our exact location.
So we're not burying anything.
You're gonna get me out of here. okay?
Plus. if they see graves here.
they'll know there are survivors.
That wouldn't be very smart. right?
We're here. this is your drop zone.
That chopper of yours is below.
I can't stay here. or they'll see me.
Ready?
On my mark.
Hey.
You're on a roller coaster.
Three. two. one. go!
JUNGLE - VERAGUA
The wind is coming from the east.
East wind.
Do you even know where we are?
Hey.
Aren't we just going in circles?
- Is this the last one?
- Yes. this is the last one.
Search the surroundings
in every direction.
- If you find any others. kill them.
- Got it.
- Let's go.
- Search everywhere.
20 MILES AWAY FROM VERAGUA
Andy. sitrep.
I've found the chopper.
The two pilots
and the embassy employee are dead.
But I think Noa and Jack are still alive.
And Caan as well.
But I'm not sure.
I haven't found them yet.
Good luck. bro.
Make sure you're on time.
You don't know where we are.
Bunch of G.I. Joes.
Yuck. goddammit!
Do you even know where we are?
Halt.
Clear.
- Can we have a little break?
- Again?
I'm exhausted.
Sorry. okay?
Andy?
- It's me.
- Holy shit.
- Hey.
- What the fuck?
- Are you guys okay?
- How did you get here?
- Jumped from a plane.
- Jesus. dude.
Very brave and touching and all.
but where's the rest?
- There's no rest.
- There's no rest?
So you're here to serve us lunch?
He has a map.
Now we're saved. Jesus Christ. hallelujah.
He's our mission?
A fucking asswipe.
We have to hurry. They're everywhere.
Three interns from the Dutch army.
The Groningen will be offshore.
This is our pickup point.
Guys. now you listen to me for once. okay?
The wind is coming from the east.
from there. as always.
That means the beach is that way.
and the sea is over there.
- That's where we have to go.
- Okay. now we're here--
Great. a woman reading a map.
The last time someone did that--
Goddammit.
He was right. we have to go that way.
See? Jesus.
Glad you're here.
Women...
- They can't be far.
- I'm exhausted.
My feet are hurting.
- We'll eat when we find them.
- Let's hope we'll find them soon.
Guys...
Goddammit. I can't anymore.
- Come on.
- No.
Just say I'll be a bit later.
I'm exhausted.
Okay. it's getting dark.
Get some rest. I'll take first watch.
Yeah.
Where exactly is this Groningen?
Off the coast of Veragua.
waiting for Caan and the marines.
What? With Lagarto on board?
That man is a huge escalation risk.
We're in their territorial waters.
If the Veraguans find out...
They have to leave.
Now. Bruno.
Sunrise. then it's gone.
I almost put a bullet in your head.
Good to have you here.
- Shouldn't you be snoring?
- Already did.
I'll take watch.
- I'll stay with you.
- No.
We all have to snooze. so do you.
Lie down.
Roger.
Good night.
We don't have much time left.
What's that?
Listen.
Let's see what it was.
We have to go. Now!
We really have to go.
Hey. are you okay?
- Hey. hey.
- I don't know.
I killed three tangos.
Hey.
- Fuck. my phone.
- Come. we have to keep moving.
Yeah.
Satcom. this is HNLMS Groningen.
We are returning and
exiting territorial waters. Out.
Let's go.
They're gone.
Oh. fuck.
Fuck!
Let's go. hurry up.
There he is.
Hello! Hello. sir! Hey!
- It's already full.
- 2.000 dollars.
What?
Okay. come on. Come. come. Go. go!
Sorry. it's completely full.
I don't want that.
Hey. let's go! Come on!
I'm sorry.
We didn't have a choice.
We should've dumped that Lagarto.
Yes. but we need him.
Captain. we've received
a secure line message.
The HNLMS Dolfijn is in our area
and wants to know our intentions.
How shall I reply?
Can you get me on there?
This is bad.
- Mr. Prime Minister?
- Yes?
The Groningen has left.
They're leaving Caan and the marines.
Sir. can I help?
Okay. I'll try. I'll try.
Something has to be done. Menno.
This has gone on too long.
It's not enough. it never was.
Sit down. please.
Would you sit down. okay?
Please. Sit down!
You know that quote
about good men who do nothing?
That's us. we're those good men.
But we can't go on like that.
Andy. calm those guys down.
Call Cruz.
It's your responsibility.
Do your job.
Calm down. sir. You sit down!
Andy!
- Secure line one. sir.
- Okay.
Oh. what the fuck?
Hello?
Mr. Cruz?
No. Cruz is gone. He has fled the country.
We are the people of Veragua. Who is this?
What the fuck?
Seriously. did you arrange this?
They were around.
Thanks.
MARINE BASE PARERA - CURACAO
Marines.
It's over.
While The Hague was waiting.
the rebels unseated Cruz.
- With a little help from the Americans.
- Americans?
In exchange for our pal over there.
Keep walking.
Head down.
President Cruz then flew the coop.
He knows it's game over
when the Americans have Lagarto.
He's a walking dictator encyclopedia.
so they were very interested in him.
- Did you do this?
- I didn't do a thing.
Gather intel. don't intervene.
Welcome home.
Together?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Hey. boys.
Come here.
And often patience pays off.
Thanks to our great cooperation
with each other
and with our friends from the American
and Veraguan governments.
we have proven able
to bring all of this to a good end.
Such bullshit.
Any questions?
Attention!
Present arms!
Order arms!
Fire.
Attention!
Dismiss!
What are you going to do?
Help Dad with the resort.
and after that. I'll see.
And the marines?
Congratulations. See you in a bit.
I think others are made for it
more than me.
And that's fine.
I'm staying too.
- Curacao?
- Savaneta.
- You?
- Straight on to the next mission.
But sadly.
I can't say anything about it yet.
Wow.
I really wanted to say that.
The first female marine. ladies and gents.
The first female motherfucking marine.
Thank you. Thank you.
- Good luck. Noa.
- Thanks.
Come here.
Take care. okay?
- Will I see you again sometime?
- If I'm around.
- You think she likes--
- No.
No.
INVASION
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm